So much has happened.
I won't even pretend like I remember every little detail.
Because each day was unique in its own way.
Though most of the memories have faded or vanished completely,
some are still as vivid now as they were then.
As if they happened yesterday.
I was the one that I was the one I don't know.
Toi
I'll see you next time.
But we get to do way more on our own now that we're high schoolers, which is great.
Uh-huh. Except at night.
Oh, yeah. Your tattoos. Will you be able to take baths?
I don't think so, no. But I'm fully prepared to go without them for the whole trip.
Too bad boys don't have private baths in their rooms like the girls.
Gonna change clothes at least?
In the bathroom stall.
I see. Good luck.
Will I enjoy this trip, like, at all?
Will he enjoy this trip, like, at all?
There you guys are! Took you long enough, huh?
Sup, shoes?
Yeah!
Where'd everyone else go?
Um...
You're yelling scared in my bed.
Who's what did what?
Lookie!
I got souvenirs from the shop up ahead.
Had to strike while the iron was hot.
Souvenirs on day one?
Dude, why load up with more junk to carry before you make it to the hotel?
Ah, that's a good point. Let's eat them now!
Wanna help me out, Miyamura?
Um, I, uh...
The kid's nuts to go and buy that stuff right off the bat.
Her enthusiasm just evaporated.
Hey, aren't you and Yorta in the same room?
Yeah, me, him, and Ishikawa.
It'll be fun.
Something tells me it won't.
This bed is so soft.
The whole room's even better than I thought it'd be.
But having free time till dinner is pretty worthless.
There's nothing to do.
You got that right.
Let's crash another room.
Ooh, like a boy's room?
Maybe.
If neither of us grab the key...
Shu picked it up, then disappeared.
What are you two doing?
Oh.
We're waiting. Shu has our room key.
Seen him around, Mizuchi?
Sure.
Saw him waltz into that room a minute ago.
Open this door right now, you idiot!
Let us in!
My bad for napping.
Not mad that you napped!
I'm mad you didn't let us in first!
At least our stuff is in the room now.
Why don't we take it easy till dinner?
You know, that's not a bad idea.
What's our time frame looking like anyway?
Hang on.
I'll check.
Shu?
Are you awake?
Maybe I'll take a nap too.
Oh!
We have to hop in the bath before dinner, right?
Do we?
Oh, crap.
Let's get squeaky clean!
No!
Let's not!
Stop being so shy!
Everyone here is a pro!
I'm gonna take my bath later.
Hey!
Move it along, group one.
There's a line.
Please help me, Ishikawa!
I think he's feeling sick.
Oh, you have a fever?
Or a cold?
Or, well, not a cold exactly.
He's not normal sick.
He's on his period.
Oh, you have those?
Come on, what's the holdup, guys?
Go take your dumb baths.
Dude, shut up!
We're dealing with an existential crisis in here!
What?
Hey, so, that was a good cover, right?
Good cover.
And goodbye.
Hey, what's going on?
Apparently, I'm on my period right now.
This is from the guy who got top marks in Phys Ed?
You've got to be kidding!
That was your excuse to get out of the public bath?
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, so then you aren't taking one at all?
Nope.
Cramps are pretty intense, so I'm gonna pass.
You know, the shower in our room is free.
Yuki went to visit with a friend and won't be back for a while.
Uh, but we'd get in trouble.
A guy showering in a girl's room?
Oh, well, only if you want to.
You don't have to.
I feel so alive.
You could have taken your time and used the hairdryer.
I don't think either of us could afford for me to take my time.
Do you hear from Yoshikawa?
Not yet.
Cool.
I should prep my stuff for tomorrow while I have the chance.
Be honest.
Would you just let any guy in your room if they were between a rock and a hard place?
You shouldn't, Tori.
Which is why I wouldn't do it.
Really?
Really.
You let me inside, though.
Because you're not like that.
You'd never, you know?
So why even pretend like you are when you aren't?
Aren't what?
What am I?
You're a trustworthy kind of guy.
You wouldn't try something.
Sure about that?
I should be getting back to my own hotel room.
Thanks again for the shower.
Wait.
Hey!
So if I said he could try something, he would?
And why'd he ask about letting other guys in my room anyway?
I took her towel.
Oh, there you are.
Yay!
You can join the Yukata Club, too!
Where have you been all night, dude?
Well, um, just out.
Whoa!
Over there!
My go at ten o'clock!
It's really good point!
Whoa!
Hey there, ladies!
Wait, that them?
I'll give your towel back later.
We have plenty more.
But speaking of, what's your plan for tonight?
Huh?
To wash up?
I'll handle Yuki if you come over.
Oh, don't worry.
Huh?
There's a late bath for people who miss their time slot.
I can go then.
That's convenient?
Should have read the itinerary more carefully.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Thanks for waiting.
Your turn!
Sure about that?
Now I feel plain stupid for thinking so much about how to respond.
And why wait till today to read the rules?
Hori?
You gonna take a bath or what?
Yup!
And not coming out till 11pm!
You'll be a prune.
This class trip flew by so freaking fast!
Sure did.
Parting's such sweet sorrow, but bye for now, Kyoto.
We've got pics to remember it!
Ooh!
And I've got space for more!
Gimme a peace sign!
Stop it, Yuki!
I'll make you copies when I get these printed, kay?
Thanks, girl.
Between yours and our teacher's photos, we'll have a ton!
Look at you, Yura, messing with Toadu!
That was really funny.
Here's East-dubbing your face.
Hope we come back together when we're older.
Same.
Hey!
They want us on the buses, like now!
We're on our way!
Over too soon.
Race all y'all to the bus!
Oh, it is on!
Miyamura!
This was a pretty nice class trip, huh?
Yeah, it was.
Get the light out, slowpokes!
Coming!
Miyamura?
Oh, wow!
It really is you!
Just with shorter hair!
Turn off the hose before you can go!
I keep talking!
Ugh!
Remy didn't realize!
Sorry!
You're absolutely soaked, huh?
It's fine.
I'll wring myself out later.
That won't do, though!
Dry off with the towel!
The nurse has some!
We...
need the nurse for this?
Ta-da!
Um, thanks a lot.
Can we use these when the nurse isn't even here?
You should maybe lose the card again.
I'll leave it.
Uh-huh.
Remy's really curious why you always keep your skin covered up.
You didn't even take baths with the other boys during the class trip to Kyoto.
Not to mention you opt for running marathons over swimming when it's hot up.
Like, who does that?
I'll tell you who does that!
Your boyfriend, the student council president!
Yes, but that doesn't bug me at all.
Why not?
Speaking of Sengoku, he told me that you only change in bathroom stalls in empty classrooms.
So, how come?
Dang it.
She's more stubborn than I thought.
Ah!
What the heck?
I thought you might be a girl, so I checked you for boobs.
My face and physique aren't girly enough, though, are they?
Ah, homegirl suspicious.
She'll find me out.
I know it.
But I'm tired.
And very hot.
And the truth comes out.
I was thinking, what if you wore a sweater vest?
Arm tats would show.
Huh.
Yet you'll wear a sailor-style uniform.
I have the chance, but why?
I really don't get what's going on in Hori's head.
I'll try it on.
Tell it it was too small, since there's no way it'll fit.
And that'll be that.
Ah, hello, Toru!
Come on in.
Sorry, I didn't call it Ed.
He's in his room.
Hey!
Need to bump a textbook off you.
I forgot mine back at school.
And since you live closer...
Wait, what's wrong, dude?
Please, stop now!
I'm excited!
It's...
It's not what you think, Ishikawa.
I swear.
I...
Think you're rocking it.
That was not what it looked like!
So what?
You won't wear one again?
You should reconsider, man.
Nah, but maybe with different hair?
Yeah, a bit longer, but not too much.
Shoulder length.
Or until it hides your ears, maybe.
Enough with the mental makeover, all right?
The plan is to grow it out for six months.
I veto this plan.
What's so great about being a sailor uniform?
That sight turned you way off before.
No, it didn't.
You rocked it.
And I said it's more...
Well, excuse me for trying to block that memory.
I seem to run into them a lot lately.
President!
Set, go down!
Blazers or sailor suits?
Which one is better?
Uh-huh?
For me, the sailor style's where it's at.
That silhouette steals my breath every single time.
No, blazers are way more versatile.
They work with both neckties and ribbons.
Right, Prez?
What crazy conversation did I just stumble into?
You know, men's fantasies.
Girl clothes that turn dudes on.
Oh, clothing preferences.
That's right.
This guy's trying to convince me that sailor suits are the way to go.
I prefer gym clothes.
Oh, I mean, they each their own...
What? That's not weird!
Ad-Lock wears super sexy!
Now, when you say gym clothes, you really mean school bathing suits, right?
If that's actually true, you're hardcore!
What's up?
Then it's the gym bloomers.
Know what year we live in?
If those aren't trendy these days, what is?
Navy blue socks.
They're like my...
Miyamura likes blazers.
And black knee hikes, too.
Okay, that I get behind.
Yes, but that doesn't bug me at all.
Why not?
Your shirt's a little on the baggy side, isn't it?
Think so?
They're all this way.
I like his slender body.
He's self-conscious about it,
and always puts shirts on underneath his button-down.
But...
Remy's well aware.
No way!
You both were really caught off guard, huh?
Yeah, swimming's optional,
except the last day when the boys have to participate.
Well, no one told us that!
Because the rule just changed this year.
This printout details it, and you all got one.
And you can't be absent without a good excuse, either.
Like a broken leg?
Don't be reckless, Miyamura!
This isn't fair!
Why only the boys?
I know!
I couldn't agree with you more!
For different reasons!
Always and forever,
I will question the ones who let you teach.
I'm pretty intelligent,
and I like high school girls.
Express this man!
Hey, back to the swimming.
It's just one day, so go on and do it.
Can I jump in dressed like this?
I'd also prefer wearing normal clothes.
Sure, if you want to drown.
The issue's the swim trunks?
My clothes are like a second layer of skin to me,
if you can grasp that.
Are you saying you'd have a student rip off his own skin,
leaving him to bake under the scorching sun
and boiling chlorine?
Calm down, Sengoku.
This just in.
Student skinned alive by cruel school.
But don't make up scary headlines.
We have four days left.
If only the world would end!
Wait, four days?
Then I have a legit excuse.
Oh?
This ought to be good.
My cycle will start again,
because it hits every 28 days.
You talking about what I think you're talking about?
Hey!
I'm cheating!
I forgot!
My cycle's also gonna start!
Mr. President!
Drop the crap right now.
No matter how much you whine,
you're doing this whether it suits you guys or not.
Oh.
Well, nothing suits, if you follow me.
No, but I'd like to follow.
Thing is, I don't have a bathing suit to call my own.
Nice try, kid.
But the school's prepared for that
and let students like you rent swimsuits for free.
Oh, wow.
Lucky you.
Yeah.
Why don't the ladies have a pool and get free swimsuits?
Because people like you exist, clearly.
I never should have applied to Katagiri.
But without this school, you wouldn't have met Hori.
So, fair trade.
Don't sell me short.
I still would have met her.
Watch her tongue, old man.
I'll expel you, punk.
Four days from now, I hope my arm explodes when I wake up.
Can't you just fake a cold?
Fine, a cold it is.
A cold that makes my entire arm explode.
What kind of colds do you typically catch?
At least you can wear a swimsuit, Prez, while I'm left to suffer.
Whatever it is you're hiding sounds tremendous.
I see.
All this because you're ashamed to be seen without a shirt.
How is wearing shorts in a pool any different from going to English naked?
Are those two things not the same?
You're talking to your English teacher, idiot.
I'd rather be publicly guillotined than be seen in a swimsuit.
Okay, I really don't get why this is a matter of life and death for you, Prez.
What I do get is that you boys don't want in that pool.
So, I'll talk to Sasaki and see what I can do.
You're kidding!
Except you better not be!
Speak to your elders politely.
You really?
Rook!
That your idea of polite?
I can't believe my ears.
You'll actually talk to Coach Sasaki?
Yeah, I'll talk to him.
Happy?
No promises, though.
It's a teacher's duty to listen to student concerns if I'm proper solutions!
Put it like that.
Now I'm nervous.
In four days' time, the clubs will stay on!
It's with the aggression.
I still need a valid reason from both of you.
I was in an explosion, and it's his time of the month.
That's all.
Those are the excuses you want me to tell him?
Honestly, no.
Compromises led us to those results.
This is gonna be a pain.
Ah, what a relief.
I wasn't sure what I'd do.
Could go for a beach day.
What?
Come on, no cannonballs allowed!
Nothing beats the pool!
How are you not hot in that getup?
Oh, I'm very hot.
That'll be okay.
You're making me hot!
Hey, get to work, slackers!
I want a spotless!
Yes, sir.
Jeez!
It's like walking on lava!
Did you not think to bring some sandals?
Rami took them before I got here.
Then take a dip and cool off!
What if I was alone?
What are you, a girl?
Send go for the flash!
You're asking for it.
That's right, so bring it first!
We were just clowning around a little.
I want a clean deck, not clouds!
You guys good?
How's it going, shrinking violets?
Working hard?
Whoa, Kyochan.
It's not that shocking.
You skipping class?
Earl's got out at noon.
See ya!
Oh, hey, Brummie, can I have my sandals?
No way, Jose!
I'm not ever giving them back.
They look comfy.
They are!
I hear the sweet sound of babes.
Where?
Ayasaki's feet are ours to behold.
Okadao-chudu-winnu-do-chizu-ruh!
Get back in the pool, you flaming water demon!
You totally missed it!
What happened?
What part of the world clean don't you understand?
Sorry.
Why are we scrubbing the deck when it's not even dirty, though?
My thoughts exactly.
Hey!
How goes, guys?
Savior!
Messiah!
Don't call me that.
It bothers me.
How are you not burning up in that thing?
Oh, I am.
My answer never changes.
Getting tired of hearing that one, huh?
So, did you just stop by to say hey?
Got bored because the girls were released early.
Ugh, it's a sausage fest.
I kind of figured that was the case.
Mr. Yasuda!
Mr. Ajima.
You're outside when I put you in charge of the boys' supplemental class!
Are you stupid or something?
Yeah.
Very possible.
He said he was intelligent four days ago.
Honestly.
I don't have time for this nonsense.
Your legs are like the size of my pinky, man.
That isn't by choice, you know.
Do you know your hip measurements?
No.
Better question for you.
Never learn how to swim?
I did.
I'm practically like a fish.
I become invincible as soon as I hit the water.
Far more than my element, it's also my domain.
Could have fooled me, landlubber.
Technically, I really like swimming, too.
That's rich, coming from a guy skipping pool day.
But I know that's only because he wants to keep his ink secret.
Mike, let's do it!
Don't die!
You did that Inugami clan handstand thing, Majiggy, didn't you?
I won't deny it, but, yeah, I did.
So you did.
Hmm?
Come to think of it, why were the two of them excused from actual swimming?
Seemed fine to me.
Sengoku's arm combusted, while Miyamura's on his period.
Uh, huh.
Huh?
Well, it is summertime.
Bound to be a Big Bang or two.
Huh?
Bound to be a Big Bang.
Ah, You can't do that, what do you mean by the night you want?
You, that way I learned from this, you know,
I thought you were trying to follow your嗤KEY zone as well
You, you can tell me you're talking about it.
Oh, oh oh oh
You